<resources>

    <!--slider-->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <!--slider-->


    <string name="app_name">Teen Patti</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>
    <string name="language_hindi">हिंदी</string>
    <string name="language_gujarati">ગુજરાતી</string>
    <string name="language_marathi">मराठी</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="table_boot">Boot Value:</string>
    <string name="table_pot">Pot Limit:</string>
    <string name="table_max">Max Bet:</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="backtolobby">BACK TO LOBBY</string>
    <string name="standup">STAND-UP</string>
    <string name="nxtround">STAND-UP\nNEXT ROUND\n</string>
    <string name="switchtble">SWITCH TABLE</string>
    <string name="festival">Festival</string>
    <string name="places">Places</string>
    <string name="sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="mood">Mood</string>
    <string name="colors">Colors</string>
    <string name="selcetv">IS SELECTING THE VARIATION</string>
    <string name="cvariation">CURRENT VARIATION :</string>
    <string name="howtoplay">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="selectvariation">SELECT VARIATION</string>
    <string name="joker">Joker</string>
    <string name="ak">AK47</string>
    <string name="xboot">4x Boot</string>
    <string name="hukum">Hukum</string>
    <string name="muflis">Muflis</string>
    <string name="faceoff">FaceOff</string>
    <string name="lowestjoker">Lowest Joker</string>
    <string name="nine">999</string>
    <string-array name="count_array">
        <item>850Cr</item>
        <item>240Cr</item>
        <item>85Cr</item>
        <item>23Cr</item>
        <item>9Cr</item>
        <item>4Cr</item>
        <item>25L</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="price_array">
        <item>₹26,000.00</item>
        <item>₹7,900.00</item>
        <item>₹4,000.00</item>
        <item>₹1,200.00</item>
        <item>₹500.00</item>
        <item>₹250.00</item>
        <item>₹30.00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="specification_array">
        <item>850 Crore Chips for Power User (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>240 Crore Chips for Power User (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>85 Crore Chips for Elite Player (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>23 Crore Chips for Elite Player (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>9 Crore Chips for Power User (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>4 Crore Chips for Power User (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
        <item>25 Lakh Chips for Power User (Teen Patti-Indian Poker)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="diamond_count">
        <item>2,80,000</item>
        <item>60,000</item>
        <item>25,000</item>
        <item>5,000</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="diamond_price">
        <item>₹4,000.00</item>
        <item>₹1,000.00</item>
        <item>₹500.00</item>
        <item>₹150.00</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="msg">MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="block">BLOCK</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="achive">Achievements : Yet to come...</string>
    <string name="edittxt">Input private chat here.</string>

    <!--Instructions for 321-->
    <string name="game_prep">One deck used per round. 6 cards are dealt to each player on the table.</string>
    <string name="game_play1">• Select table level and click on "JOIN NOW" to enter the tournament.</string>
    <string name="game_play2">• 3 empty sets displayed on the bottom left side.</string>
    <string name="game_play3">• 6 cards displayed on bottom right side.</string>
    <string name="game_play4">• Place the best possible cards in the sets of 3 cards, 2 cards, 1 card respectively.</string>
    <string name="game_play4_1">◦ Assume one card in set of 2; assume two cards in set of 1.</string>
    <string name="game_play5">• Cards can be placed using any of the following methods.</string>
    <string name="game_play5_1">◦ One card at a time: Drag any one card to a particular set.</string>
    <string name="game_play5_2">◦ Multiple cards together: Click and select multiple cards then click on the set where you want to drop the cards.</string>
    <string name="game_play6">• After placing all the 6 cards in 3 sets, place "GO" button.</string>
    <string name="game_play7">• Then there will be a consecutive showdown on the table for all the 3 sets.</string>
    <string name="score1">• Winning of a set will be decided based on Teenpatti ranking of hands.</string>
    <string name="score2">• Player will get 60 points on winning a hand. So, in a single round 3 hands will be played.</string>
    <string name="score3">• Maximum 180 points can be scored in one round.</string>
    <string name="score4">• There will be total 5 rounds in the tournament with max score 900 for a single player.</string>
    <string name="score5">• In case of tie, points will be divided equally amongst the players.</string>
    <string name="score6">• Click on "PLAY AGAIN" to enter the same level tournament.</string>




    <string name="firstpoint">• Click on "6 PATTI" Button</string>
    <string name="g_play1">Set the Buy-in value using slider.Then Click on "Join Now " button.</string>
    <string name="g_play2">• Once all the players have joined,game will start.</string>
    <string name="g_play3">• Each player will get 6 cards</string>
    <string name="g_play3_1">◦ Note:Each player will be assigned wwith their own deck of cards and cards will be randomly distributed from the same.</string>
    <string name="g_play4">• Choose 3 out 6 cards to play your best suitable* chal.</string>
    <string name="g_play4_1">◦ Tap on cards that you want to select.</string>
    <string name="g_play4_2">◦ Then click on "GO" button to proceed.</string>
    <string name="g_play4_3">◦ You will get 10 seconds to complete your chaal.</string>
    <string name="g_play5">• After your chaal the selected 3 cards will be played on the table.\n
                            Note You can also view selected cards other players after their respective chaal.</string>
    <string name="g_play6">• Player with the higher hand wins.
                            (Ranking of hands is the same as in the classic Teen Patti game,refer\n
                            details at the end of the documentation) Winner will be declared after all the players have completed their chaal.</string>
    <string name="g_play7">• Then next round will start within 5 second.\n
                            3 new random cards will be distributed from your respective set.
                            These 3 along with 3 remaining cards will be your 6 cards for this round.
                            Repeat above steps to play your chaal.</string>
    <string name="g_play8">Note: There will be 5 players and 15 rounds. Deck of 45 cards will be assigned to each player in which randomly 7 cards will be removed. But those randomly removed 7 cards will be same from every deck.</string>
    <string name="g_play9">• Ranking of the players will be declared at the end of the tournament. Ranks will be given based on the number of rounds won by a player and winner takes it all.</string>
    <string name="g_play9_1">* If its not your first chance then you can play smartly. You can decide your cards by looking at other players cards. If your best cards cant make you win that round, then better save it for next round and give away the worst ones. Hence, the best suitable chaal.</string>
    <string name="g_play10">• Trail - three cards of the same rank.
                            Three aces are the best trail and three twos are the lowest.</string>
    <string name="g_play11">• Straight run - three consecutive cards of the same suit.
                            A-2-3, which is the highest straight run. Next comes A-K-Q, K-Q-J and so on down to 4-3-2, which is the lowest.</string>
    <string name="g_play12">• Normal run - three consecutive cards, not all of the same suit.
                            A-2-3 is the best normal run, then A-K-Q, K-Q-J and so on down to 4-3-2.</string>
    <string name="g_play13">• Color - any three cards of the same suit.</string>
    <string name="g_play14">• Pair - two cards of the same rank.\n
                            Between two such hands, compare the pair first, then the odd card if these are equal.
                            The highest pair hand is therefore A-A-K and the lowest is 2-2-3. </string>
    <string name="g_play15">• High card - three cards that do not belong to any of the above types. Compare the highest card first, then the second highest, then the lowest. The best hand of this type is A-K-J of mixed suits, and the worst is 5-3-2 </string>
    <string name="g_play16">Any hand of a higher type beats any hand of a lower type </string>
    <string name="sixpatti_infogame">This cards have been discarded for this tournament : </string>
    <string name="tourney_info">This is a high stakes knock-out tournament where you can win 5 times your buy in amount. All players start with the same number of chips. Players get knocked out when their balance chips become less than 10 times the boot value for the next round. The boot value will increase after every 2 rounds. There is a Force Show if any player does not have enough chips to place the next bet. In this case the dealer lends the player the balance chips. In case the player wins the round, 2 times the borrowed chips are returned to the dealer. </string>
    <string name="round_won_tourney">Rounds Won</string>
</resources>
